Andrew Baron

806 Weatherly Court Longwood FL, 32750 407-312-7589 BaronAndrew01@gmail.com

Technical Skills:

Proficiency in HTML5, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, JQuery, AngularJS. Experience working in a team or solo based environment. Experience with version control - Git and Github.

Object oriented programming - Using classes to organize program architecture.

Work Experience:

Real Digital Media

2008 - 2010, 2013-2016

- Exposure to Ruby on Rails and Linux
 - -Player setup performed with Linux commands.
- Shipping
 - -Receiving, testing, and shipping quantities of multimedia players.
- Setun
 - -Installation of operating systems and content on multimedia players.
- Skills
 - -Communication
 - -Time management
 - -Attention to detail

Costco Wholesale

December 2012 - January 2013

- Full Time Seasonal.
 - -High paced environment

Books-A-Million

July 2012 - September 2012

- Information desk help.
 - -Helping customers find books
 - -Calming frustrated customers
- · Cashier.
 - -Experience with creating rapid connections with customers
- · Cafe barista.
 - -Experience with a fast paced environment
 - -Attention to detail and memory of complex orders

Silver Divorce Center

August 2011 - July 2012

- · Clerk & Receptionist.
 - -Experience with calming frustrated clients.
 - -Experience with making rapid connections with clients and creating a positive atmosphere.

Education:

The Iron Yard Durham

Feb 2016-Present

Seminole State College of Florida

Associate of the Arts Degree